myprivacyswitch.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy Switch

**Last Updated: October 25, 2016**

This privacy policy (“ **Policy** ”) describes how plasko interactive Ltd. and its related companies (“ **Company** ”) collect, use and share personal information of consumer users of this website, www.myprivacyswitch.com (the “ **Site** ”). This Policy also applies to any of our other websites that post this Policy. This Policy does not apply to websites that post different statements.

**WHAT WE COLLECT**

We do not collect any personally identifying information about you. The only information that we collect is the search terms (in an anonymous form) that you enter into the search box. By anonymous, we mean that these search terms are never linked to any information about you, because we do not collect information about you.

**USE OF INFORMATION**

We use the search terms that you enter into the search box to provide search results to you and to optimize and improve our service.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We may share the anonymous search terms with others for in order to serve you search results and advertisements within the browser.

**CONTACT INFORMATION.**

We welcome your comments or questions about this privacy policy or our service. You may also contact us at [support@myprivacyswitch.com](mailto:contact@privacyswitch.com).  

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

We may change this privacy policy. If we make any changes, we will change the Last Updated date above.

**Last Updated: October 26, 2016**

This privacy policy (“ **Policy** ”) describes how plasko interactive Ltd. and its related companies (“ **Company** ”) collect, use and share personal information of consumer users of this website, www.myprivacyswitch.com (the “ **Site** ”). This Policy also applies to any of our other websites that post this Policy. This Policy does not apply to websites that post different statements.

**WHAT WE COLLECT**

We do not collect any personally identifying information about you. The only information that we collect is anonymous information, such as the search terms that you enter into the search box, browser version and type, internet protocol address, and operating system and type. By anonymous, we mean that these search terms and other information are never linked to any information about you, because we do not collect information that identifies you.

**WHAT WE _DON’T_ COLLECT**

We _do not_ collect your name, telephone number, email address, social security number, username, geographic location, referring URL (the website that you came from to download our extension), or the websites you visit. Why? Because then you wouldn’t be anonymous.

**USE OF INFORMATION**

We use the anonymous information that we collect to provide search results to you and to optimize and improve our service.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We may share the anonymous information we collect with others for in order to serve you search results and advertisements within the browser.

**CONTACT INFORMATION.**

We welcome your comments or questions about this privacy policy or our service. You may also contact us at [support@myprivacyswitch.com](mailto:support@myprivacyswitch.com).  

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

We may change this privacy policy. If we make any changes, we will change the Last Updated date above.
